<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Humans of Nosara</title>
    <link>https://www.humansofnosara.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Humans of Nosara</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 13:25:52 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.humansofnosara.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mario Antonio Reyes Hernandez</title>
      <link>https://www.humansofnosara.org/human/mario-antonio-reyes-hernandez/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 17:33:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.humansofnosara.org/human/mario-antonio-reyes-hernandez/</guid>
      <description>I have lived in Nosara all my life. I love to be surrounded by all the people from town who I have known since I was a child whilst also being in touch with the new people and being able to learn from them. A group of people who I think should receive some attention are the children who live in the poorer areas of town. I would love to make a positive improvement in their lives and I believe the idea of a recreational center which opens doors to better opportunities is a good start.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fritz Elmendorf, Organico</title>
      <link>https://www.humansofnosara.org/human/fritz-elmendorf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 17:33:17 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.humansofnosara.org/human/fritz-elmendorf/</guid>
      <description>Back home I was a journalist. I started in Kentucky but after a couple of years landed a job in DC working for a congressman. After that, I did public relations and writing for trade associations for many years. My girlfriend asked me twenty years ago to come to Nosara for a yoga trip and I bought some land on my first visit. This made it possible for me to setup a home and for my first three years here I was barbecuing with the community and writing articles for The Voice of Nosara (now known as The Voice of Guanacaste).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paola Pao Barrera</title>
      <link>https://www.humansofnosara.org/human/paola-pao-barrera/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 20:00:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.humansofnosara.org/human/paola-pao-barrera/</guid>
      <description>I was born on the north coast of Peru. I grew up in a place close to the sea and since I was a little girl I’ve had a passion for the surf like my family, although I didn’t learn how to surf until I came to Costa Rica when I was 16. After that I travelled to many different parts of the country and 6 years ago I found Nosara, the place where I came to get my yoga instructor certification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gustavo Miranda Cambronero, El Mystiko Kolibri</title>
      <link>https://www.humansofnosara.org/human/gustavo-miranda-cambronero/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 16:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.humansofnosara.org/human/gustavo-miranda-cambronero/</guid>
      <description>My name is Gustavo Miranda Cambronero but you can call me Tao. I first arrived in Sámara looking for a new way of life because I found the city too complicated and monotonous, it is always the same scene with different characters, I wanted something more than that. I started studying arts and it was in this moment that I realised that cooking was my thing. I noticed when I put my food on the table the entire energy of the room changed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volunteer</title>
      <link>https://www.humansofnosara.org/volunteer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 16:13:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.humansofnosara.org/volunteer/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>